simplylearnt.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy - simplylearnt.com

**_Privacy Policy_**

  Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy.

    \- We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes  
    \- We will never share your contact information with any other user without your consent  
    \- Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the simplyLearnt service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.

  Please read this privacy policy to learn more about:

    * What personally identifiable information of yours is collected by SimplyLearnt?  
    * How your personal information is used.  
    * With whom the information may be shared.  
    * How can you access and change your Account information.  
    * What security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information collected by SimplyLearnt?  
    * How can you contact us?

Information Collection

  **Registration** :  
In order to become a SimplyLearnt user, you must first create an account on this web site. To create an account you are required to provide the general contact information like name, email address, and choose a password.

  **Profile Information** :  
We collect your personal details to maintain your user account on SimplyLearnt. Your profile includes general details like your address information, contact phone numbers, and alternate email address. We give you full autonomy to keep this information private or public. These particulars help us maintain your up to date contact information on our records and to serve you better.

  **Cookies & Log Files**:  
Like most web sites, SimplyLearnt uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file saved on your computer to allow SimplyLearnt to recognize you as a user whenever you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies you will not be able to use our website. Like the information that you enter at registration or in your profile, in the cookie and in the log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.

  Complying with the communication standards on the Internet, we automatically receive the URLs of the sites you previously surfed and moved on while your visit to SimplyLearnt site. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the SimplyLearnt service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

  **Children** :  
Children can only use our services under the supervision of their parents/legal guardians and we always suggest minors (under the age of 13) not to submit any personal information to us or use the service.

  **Information Use**  
SimplyLearnt is an online service dedicated to help all students and tutors to connect more effectively with one another. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself to other users. Other information, that does not personally identify you as an individual is collected by SimplyLearnt from the site (such as, by way of example, patterns of utilization) and is exclusively owned by SimplyLearnt. This information can be utilized by SimplyLearnt in such a manner as SimplyLearnt, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

  **SimplyLearnt Communications** :  
SimplyLearnt will communicate with you through email and notices posted on SimplyLearnt website. This includes a series of welcome emails (up to 5) that inform new users about various features of the service. Please be aware that you will always receive emails from SimplyLearnt concerning the proper functioning of your account such as email notices when another user in your network sends you an opportunity. SimplyLearnt may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, please send a request to support@simplyLearnt.com.

  **Customized Content** :  
Information you provide at the time of registration or maintain in your Profile is also used to customize your experience on the web site. For example, when you login to your account we will display the screen names of new users who have made a request to use your teaching services.

  **Information Sharing**

  **Sharing Information with Third Parties** :  
SimplyLearnt takes the privacy of its users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third party or parties for marketing purposes. We will only share this information with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide you specific services. For instance, we use the services of a credit card processing company to bill our users for site usage fees. These third parties do not retain, share, or store this personally identifiable information or its part other than a purpose to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

  SimplyLearnt offers a “web profile” feature which allows users to publish portions of their SimplyLearnt profile, including your “name”, but not your “email address” to the public Internet. Users may opt-out of this feature however SimplyLearnt does not warrant how third-party search engines will update their cache.

  We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by role (i.e. students, adult learner), subject, geographic location, or by company. If you would like to be excluded from the aggregated research or products based upon aggregated data about our users’ activities on the site, please email SimplyLearnt’s customer service.

  **Partnering with Other Organizations to Offer Combined Services** :  
SimplyLearnt partners with other online services to give you the combined results of both services. Whenever we offer such combined services, it will always be your choice to make use of the combined services or not. In these cases, your personally identifiable information will only be passed from SimplyLearnt to our partner if you choose to use the combined service.

  **Communications between Users** :  
Many emails you initiate through SimplyLearnt, will list your email address and name in the header of the message. Other communications that you initiate through the SimplyLearnt website, like a request for teacher, will list your name as the initiator but will not include your personal contact information. Your contact information will only be shared with another user if both of you have indicated your interest to establish contact with each other.

  **Web Beacons** :  
Webpages and HTML emails may contain a small snippet of code called a web beacon. In their simplest form, web beacons allow a website to transfer or collect information through a graphic image request. Websites may use web beacons and cookies for many purposes, including site usage analytics, advertising auditing and reporting, and content and advertising personalization.

**SimplyLearnt's Practices Regarding Web Beacons**  
SimplyLearnt may collect information through web beacons about your web browsing activities such as the address of the page you are visiting, the address of the referrer page you previously visited, the time you are viewing the page, your browsing environment and your display settings. We may use the information we collect through web beacons:

  * To understand how you use and interact with SimplyLearnt's products and services.
  * To improve SimplyLearnt products and services.
  * To optimize your browsing experience.
  * To provide you relevant advertising and content.
  * To determine which email messages sent by SimplyLearnt, or its agent, were opened and to note whether a message was acted upon.

  **Legal Disclaimer** :  
It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

  **Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**  
You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your SimplyLearnt account any time by logging into your account on the SimplyLearnt website and editing the information on your Profile page. You can also close your account on the SimplyLearnt website. If you close your SimplyLearnt account, we will remove your name and other personally identifiable information from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the SimplyLearnt Privacy Policy that you have previously agreed to. To request that we close your account and remove your information from the SimplyLearnt service, please send your request to support@simplyLearnt.com. Please send your request using an email account that you have registered with SimplyLearnt under your name. You will receive a response to requests sent to support@simplyLearnt.com within seven business days of our receiving it.

  **Security**  
All private information like your address or credit card number or PayPal account number can be accessed only by providing your password.

  **Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
SimplyLearnt may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we process your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

  **Questions or Comments**  
If you have questions or comments about this privacy policy, please email us at info@simplyLearnt.com or contact us at: www.SimplyLearnt.com

Kamal Learning Solutions Pvt. Ltd.  
Attn: Privacy Policy issues  
F 46/A, Moti Nagar,

New Delhi 110015, India
